dreamhorse.com 2004-06-30

# Dream Horse Classifieds - Privacy Statement

##  Privacy Statement for Dream Horse Classifieds 

**Dream Horse Classifieds** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [ Dream Horse Classifieds ](http://www.dreamhorse.com/)

####  Information Automatically Logged 

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. __

####  Cookies 

Our Site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart. We also use cookies to save your user ID, password, name, and email address so you don't have to re-enter them each time you visit our site. These are also used on the horse ads as a way to make it easier for you to send inquiries to the horse owners. 

#### Third-Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

####  Third Party Advertising 

 

We use BurstMedia and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

####  Registration Forms 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information like their name, email, and postal address. We display the horse owner's contact name, contact email, contact phone, contact fax, city, state and postal code with the horse ad. We do not display an owner's street address. The only required field is contact email. Dream Horse Classifieds is offering a new service called TackTrader.com. Your Dream Horse contact information will also work on TackTrader.com if you choose to use TackTrader.com. 

Contact information (email address) from the registration forms is used to get in touch with the customer when necessary such as informing the customer that their horse or tack ad is expiring. Contact information may also be shared with any law enforcement agency investigating any fraudulent or improper activity on Dream Horse Classifieds or TackTrader.com.

Dream Horse does not and will never sell or give your email address to any SPAMMERS or JUNK MAILERS. We hate spam and will do everything possible to protect your information. We have recently begun hiding your email address completely so that we can track and screen any and all responses to your ads by forcing responses through our owner contact form. 

####  Order Forms 

Our site uses secure online ordering for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect financial information when orders are placed for photo ads. The information that is collected is used to enable the user to pay for for products and services with our secure shopping cart system. It is not used for any other purpose. Our secure storefront is called the [DreamHorse Store](http://store.dreamhorse.com/). 

####  Surveys 

Our online surveys ask visitors for demographic information (like zip code, age, or income level). 

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.   
This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

####  External Links 

This site contains links to other sites. **Dream Horse Classifieds** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

####  Special Relationships 

  * Our message board is hosted by [Delphi Forums](http://www.delphi.com/)
  * Our guestbook is hosted by [Guest World](http://www.guestworld.com/). 
  * We host banner ads from BurstMedia. Please see their [Privacy Statement](http://www.burstmedia.com/release/privacy.asp). 
  * We may host banner ads from the Sonar Network, a Division of DoubleClick.net. Please see their [Privacy Statement](http://www.sonar.com/content/privacy.htm) also. 

####  Public Forums 

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

####  Security 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We do not save your credit card information online on our server. Your personal information is password protected by your User ID and password. 

####  Data Quality/Access 

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: 

  1. You can update your user information at any time by logging in and updating it through a form. 

##  Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:   

Contact Information
